The next expert in the whole is
Pradeep Chaudhary Pradeep is the
founder of GPS Capital and is a firm that works in
investment advisory and premature ejaculation.
Thank you for the coming time. There is
no need to be afraid that everything is fine. Now I will
tell you after a long time, after almost 3
months I am subscribing and I am saying that as you will
see in the next time that it is running at 24, 25, 20, 30.
Only work can be done at 15, 15, 16. If there is water then only
time is telling that somewhere in the market the
affair level is very low for these
spectrum.
This is another set of company with market effort. I believe that the market is currently
running at 15700 duty. In the
short term, if I think that 16000,
16501 fact, who knows, even in this year if
we reach 17000 then it will not be a big deal
because a mistake has started
in the market and which brand  What will happen
sir sometimes correction will come, on that correction
we will take entry here
we should think about that stock
specific we should go, so I
was not in the stock market right now, current
never thought anything wrong,
saved some money, it went up and down, Radha went down,
so we always have to
return the bank opportunities also,
okay so today's fall is a
good opportunity, this type of dress can get more, there can be a
bigger fall than this, to
enter, it is unknown for new people to
make a new position, for them dress like
Salman took with Modi, I will tell you once,
recruits will wait a bit, but bloody
politicians like this you can take position here also because
if you know how to manage your entire skin
tightening, then
you can achieve this, I believe this
promise can
come up to 2650, so whenever 15750 will be
your problem because anyone who
wants to enter can make a good appointment,
but if anyone
searches for mapping t-shirts then he can watch this video  I ca
n't see it, I want to enter Punjab as well, that's why I should be
investing in these for
Indian scripts, so gift is my
Superintendent of Police, what is the mill quantity,
what is the medical management, find out,
I will work with that Pradeep ji, today
we do not have an opportunity to do some work in the market,
I will suggest you some of the viewers,
in the crucial moment, I will
not say anything short term just for the internet, I will tell you about the
position, a
very good chapter in professional, where
today after years, a week ago, policy, now
after appointing to score,
subscribe, so I am subscribing now, so I
believe that I am not saying this because
now
I will talk about school, I will talk about impressed, it is
possible that this problem may be created in blood relatives,
so the investment of these banks will be
a good
stuffing there, Kabir, now take out the interview, according to that, I agree for the
better, justice is being made,
457 in India, so 457 I have
subscribed to you first, that is why I have subscribed to
Celery is 209,
thankfully, right now children 465 467 are running, so I am
not going to do it just because of this, we will
also use Nifty, scientific needs
to be soot from IIM in foreign delegates, as
I told you that Niti is
giving breakup to intermediate parliamentary parties
and manipulative in interviews,
then the interest piece of fog and cold, if anyone
can buy a good chikoo for a minimum of 151, not for market page setup, if
anyone wants to invest in a system, then
I believe sir, this is
also a human being or
Telugu, the
indication will be productive work and
effect will be felt that if anyone
invests in Muslim, this will easily give
3051 return, it will be beneficial, spring, it is
not very simple, everything can be deleted,
aloe vera juice will be done first, this will be
theirs, and till only one, which will be my target,
sir, 540 and my infra will be in the middle, it will be
beaten properly and this is the thirty first
time in life in love with Ajita, who will
want inch
This 398 minutes problem should be solved and Meera Sharma should be
sensitive. Vikas is a juicer
that if I put any specific team
in these friend tips, like if there is
anything difficult, I will tell you this,
Tushar Mukesh Bhatt, but this one is the same
famous one, even though there is
maximum here, but the quantity of Britain is
very high, this thing is a strategy, let me
also tell dear viewers that what are you doing,
Pradeep's members are doing that by
listening to the stock, keep it straight for 10 minutes
inside it because there
we are at a little bit of a Krishna stage and the
market can go up and down at any time, good quality
or some such things, otherwise it is
strong, but you can get good
prices, your prices could have gone bad if you entered now,
hence Pradeep Bhaiya has
brought out one thing for me for making a new kitchen,
he is saying that
in these for the middle, if you buy with a stop loss of 390 for
3 to 4 months or for four to
five minutes  If done, then targets ranging
from 480 to
540, 680 can be seen on it. The
good thing is that it is on this
side, so it is intact in this way,
which is a very positive
idea. If there is any fall, then its effect will be
very little or not at all on it, so to a
great extent we are at peace that there is
no need to worry about stop loss in this,
but due to discipline and to
treat it in a good way, we have made
surplus suggested labels,
but perhaps he says Pradeep ji,
you will not have to worry about stop loss and it
may be that it will easily suit you well,
right perimeter, see this, in the year
2008, there was a cup of doing it in 2010,
after that it was done in 2013, it happened, so now
after that
it happened till Jhaal, after that I
also tried once, it happened, I
believe, when in 2008, today
see the breakout, picture locate again which  It is
going above 13 points, first of all
subscribe, that is why if you
see that you are confident and
subscribe to me and it was made on
19th, since then it has been running
but secondly it decides now and that is why
this channel is subscribing to this
entry level, okay subscribe,
momentum is visible with Congress
and now it will participate and by doing this it will
give you a good profit and at the same time one
thing is that you sit and find
some very different things, so Deep ji, in
this way we also bring such different spoons
for you so that we can
give different types of strategies, different types of opinions
and we can benefit from that, okay so
replay, apart from this there are some questions from us viewers
and so many stocks send a
little but 171 extractor, so
I have told you one and I
would like to tell you from a particular topic, first I will
tell you the name of the stock, the name of the stock
itself into end technology, and you are an
N C and
First let me tell you a little fundamental about Rural Technology stock. The
fundamentals have been done when the company was started
or the chairman of the company,
Ankit and Jagroop, it is Baat Group, it was formed
in 1995 after Hans when the company and at
this point company Del Piero company,
someone is necessary to find, the US market is
more than 30 thousand crores, the
market share of the company will participate in the accused Hussain
is set at maximum, he has given a
return of 17 votes in the last five years to the companies and I have
commented but I will talk about this comment
* I have taken a good idea of ​​this comment above 15050,
once it had reached 1616, again the
stock is in the list, so believe me,
this will be my first stop,
my first target will be 1638, after this,
sir, 1750, I will remain Radhe-Radhe, I will
subscribe and comment in the top box
or if it is 1400 or soon I will
see it in Mexico Jalal Lot, if I
see a profit then yes pass then students  800m can be
obtained anytime and when I am
telling you both the entropy schedule and technology, I am
giving you clear macros, any
investor wants to invest in short term to
medium term investments, if any investor wants to invest
two to three times,
then this can be a good opportunity for you to invest,
I have some comments for you,
Vinod Bagyal ji from the audience is saying that
Pradeep ji is very young in age but is
very confident, so he is liking it, for that he is
telling you that you should buy
long term, he was asking whether this is the right time, then he
answered that question, you have commented, then
you were already talking about both the things,
that thing is
our subscribe problem, it
seems that when people think
how can we manage us, if we
have the power, my decision, then in every tree,
if I am where, then I should have minimum one to
two on Saint Lucia.  10 to 12
budget 15 government jobs would have been found below Ghee
Lutyens Joint Secretary Management if
you are in a square for Jharkhandi and he
took his stock in his quantity by watching some other issue on TV and
wishing someone on
his own then what happened you can say
sometimes you get good profit but sometimes
you will face such a big market issue and
sir hundreds of strange people are saying the same thing that
how do you make money then show us how to make money so on my
part the big thing is that it takes
time to earn money but it does
not take time to make passenger money so on the other hand
I believe that the director captain should
set up to medium at minimum whenever I talk about short term, don't give
your best in the
museum after that I say minimum pipe
try don't look and long-term more than one
year you should fold if you have
Twitter you have to become a businessman sir before one and a half if
you
are a businessman then when you will be able to become a week then
you should always come out on profit if
you definitely Shubhendu invest in stock
market time verification object that I have
till areas  Mehak Investor, after clearing one thing,
we should come to this point
that this opinion is coming from Pradeep Andar ji
that you will have to decide, you will have to
explain yourself and understand that you are on the
side, whether on the operator side, or on the
minister side, and now you can have both,
but separate both the portfolios,
both can be of different types, otherwise the
best way would be that which I often suggest
that you open two accounts, one is a
holding account in which you have
made a bundle of all your money and kept it for long term, then you should
not go to it anytime in a hurry
because if you have made a little investment for this year, then it is of no use,
review it only after a long time, do not go into it in between and
see what is not going on in it, what loss is happening, what is happening
because it is a
long term bread, make a bundle of that and
leave it aside, keep an artist account for this trading,
if you want to do both the things,
in trading only back and those who are
giving their best, that is a lot of
loss, hence always keep that tiffin with you,
you will not incur more loss than this, that is why you do
Swapna Dosh, and there are
cigarettes there, that is yours  Discipline is
very important in trading
and in today's date, the market is of such a nature that
its importance increases even more here on description labels, do
not do any work without stop loss, okay Pradeep, I will take some questions,
one is from Priyanjali Guruji, he
wants to know
whether the exit should be attended, that is buy of
308, by 98100, but we want to subscribe one thing
upwards, there
is a deep subscribe of 550 upwards, can this
subscribe work, then 550 can
also be subscribed and the subscription is a
little more in short term medium term,
hence those questions or those who
do more in this way also, but the
way in which to subscribe from the upwards,
want to ask such questions, it is short term
that a one shot updater has been taken on Hindustan Construction
and you have a stop loss,
first the stock of Star Plus is ₹10 and the end is
rs.12, so stop love shots which is a stoploss of ₹10, the
silver date was left,
if he has come to college  This momentum stock maintained,
from will go 3150 and after that will go
1550 formation here fixed seat Hindustan
Crush popular Piramal Enterprises
accused is very important for 3 months,
Ajay has happened
so let's say interpress here, there is
a breakup after a long time, after that I have to say about this
stop, the level of those parts was many times, the
staff of Times of India
consolidated a bit, after that it
also showed itself in the form of a Basu, which was
available in the market a bit and I
opened the office which completes it,
after that the company launched it on Naira,
after this the company again tested it for a full show,
after that the print of the company came on top of it, so
when I believe three for them, right now there is
image resistance on the top side, that middle people, then
three bytes for them toss 2021 2671
update this, if Bikram Chowk you
must click on 350 26 more primary button,
if you want to buy face, then
I will give settings are not on or else
dare  One hundred point eco point can be a
good option in a quiz,
this is a question from Anurag Kumar ji on Piramal,
want to know from this and the
interview is 5 years old Tilak is very
good but I have always been
in technical field, sometimes any company's zonal
is a good quality company and there is no question of naming and
pushing for a
very company for three to four minutes, they are the
founder of this five year, you will have to maintain a big
period, that big this love is
looking a bit innocent, on that I will
say one Badna they will have to do 1100
installments, that means 40 or
you will maintain Impress Difficult Star Plus,
this is Badrinath stop, non double
people in HP can see,
cancel immediately in case of emergency, till this topic
volunteers have tremendous conductor's good,
this Agri Care is shallow, but then rickshaw wala
Rajesh ji is asking for 3 months on solar wind speed, there is
cabaret code in solar industry,
after that what did the stop do, let me first tell you what
is the complete in 2017  Research of ₹100,
after that in 2018 also same
specification, after that in 2019 also their
success, after that 15 minutes were left on the distance
side, after that you will have to do two muscle C
mystery eight and resistance Haider
of 1450 which is 1450 1408 which is one zone,
after a lot of time see the printout, the
company has given expressway curve and but
I believe that companies are running 2016 Venus,
once then in
my opinion if the person suffering from ₹50 below,
come and meet in the zone of ₹50
published in the middle zone, well there
is a passion to complete one, and if you get it then
only face target will be of school and inter
city hotel directly or first
target 1750, after that it remains 986 3000, then it can
run great on 16 gas but we will have to
maintain the problem, its effect is Pooja
Shop 34, these tricks have been told,
so Dev ji  If you get some small tips
then take them, I have told you the stop loss labels
but this method can be adopted,
look at PDFC Bank, the viewers have
asked different questions, Neeraj ji also asked, someone had
asked me that IDFC Bank is with me,
in side C bank sir, first I used to
say IDFC Bank, actually the channel is difficult to do
in banking sector, I will give
tips number one inches cement, that is why
banks like Kotak Bank, all the banks should be followed,
if there is a way, the answer is profit,
but if there is a bank loan from bank, then it has taken its
time, so I believe that
click a subscribe button on this side and you will have to
subscribe to my channel, if
I do not do it now,
I am on top,
what will happen on the rupee, it
is on charity, that feedback came 2014 exotic
members are suitable, rubbing with medicine three, so
it is possible but in this style you are running on gas,
stop, but here the typing will be done,
after that
I will present one level of these western banks, one year and
fold it, it has become ITC,
bring it to someone, this much is also in the market  It is
happening that ITC is not running for years,
NTPC is not running for 5 years,
so this is the same ITC, I am not making
time to connect with add difficulty now,
I am telling AP that it can
also work, or there is no record,
fundamentally the banking sector has
strength, very different, diet tips for myself, there is
no strength, secondly seeing the addition in ITC,
when IDBI recruitment 12404 Suthar
falling crush, only then ITC 210 enemy keep wound, you will
laugh, interview with just 15 right now market
hi glue typing ID 210 215, so this
time IT is all with Dinesh Sharma, he is
asking the question that how do you feel about
this kind of Hindustan and why is this question reported,
sir, why is the phone top, why is the company chatting,
I think strict in which zone can
you bank, a professional of 105 105,
now see, we can bank
at 125, looper at 130, after that 140,
we can get, so cosmetic is a
company,
today's situation is like this  Dinesh ji, this is a good company for you
and there are good possibilities. I
need your love. Those with a degree can go to Loop In for
5 to 6 months. I have
given a lot of details about it, but this
company was established in 1954 in June this year.
Subscribe to the video.
Thankfully, the new director and daily directors came out.
This is our first platform and this is
our opportunity.
Any problem of bike can be solved on the internet right now.
Lupin Jor Sir, that can run. It is very
good. And don't take pictures till 2 years
in Pascal. It will run a lot and keep it aside for 3 months.
I cannot tell right now
whether that Bigg Boss will close above 1250.
After that, there will be a moment in this token,
that is the first 24 carat and after that it will go to
1350, 1450, it will be 1617, then this
topic can come, but until the level of 1250 does
not enter this dream, so right now I am
not in the immediate police, we are always there, questions
and many more to join.  Yes, but right now there is a shortage of time,
we will move on to the next show on crypto
and questions there too, but
we will continue taking these questions as well, so the
questions that we have sent, we will take them from me again after this, if they are
correct in the other taps of the stock market, then we will take them from me
and move on to the accused, but apart from that
we have taken another option, so if you pay
attention, here you will find a comment which is
pinned above from Amazon, by
clicking on it the
viewers can go and
share their questions there, we will not take those questions live,
but we will collect those questions together
and by lining them up together we will take
answers from them and the
video of the answers to those questions will be published
and you will get the
information that your
questions have been answered in this video
and you will be able to watch that video, then
you will not have to search for it and we will
say that for the answers to your questions, so
this is my guarantee, my
responsibility that if we get an answer to a question
from an expert, then we will get it done
and in this way  From now on, the
country's leading experts will keep joining us.
Thank you for taking out time to add to the unexpected stock market that has been super or repacked without getting involved with them. You should sleep at this time.